{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Team communication",
					"Planning",
					"Outcome evaluation",
					"Data gathering"
				],
				"question": "Which step in EMS decision making comes after a patient has been transferred?",
				"source": "See Critical Thinking and Clinical Decision Making in EMS"
			},
			"back": "Outcome evaluation"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"that person is fired.",
					"pay is withheld.",
					"management will be changed.",
					"everyone fails."
				],
				"question": "In an interdependent group, when one person fails:",
				"source": "See Dependent, Independent, and Interdependent Groups"
			},
			"back": "everyone fails."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"does not have to wait for an assignment before performing a task.",
					"will be specifically instructed on how to perform a specific task.",
					"will rely on the group leader for making virtually all decisions.",
					"will receive no support or guidance from an EMS supervisor."
				],
				"question": "When working as an independent health care group member, the EMT should expect that he or she:",
				"source": "See Dependent, Independent, and Interdependent Groups"
			},
			"back": "does not have to wait for an assignment before performing a task."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"interdependently.",
					"dependently.",
					"under standing orders.",
					"independently."
				],
				"question": "EMTs and other health care providers function as a true team when they work:",
				"source": "See Dependent, Independent, and Interdependent Groups"
			},
			"back": "interdependently."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"there is no evidence to support the syncopal episode.",
					"the EMR was probably mistaken about the episode.",
					"the patient had a reported syncopal episode.",
					"she should contact the EMR about the incident."
				],
				"question": "EMTs arrive at the scene of an ill person. The EMR, who arrived before the EMTs, advises that the patient had a syncopal episode. The patient is conscious and alert and remains so throughout transport. When transferring patient care to the emergency department nurse, the EMT should advise the nurse that:",
				"source": "See Transfer of Patient Care"
			},
			"back": "the patient had a reported syncopal episode."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"the EMT does not trust the hospital staff.",
					"the EMT’s focus is not on the common goal.",
					"the patient’s leg does not require splinting.",
					"the EMT is being realistic in her thinking."
				],
				"question": "While caring for a patient, the EMT states to her partner, “Why even splint the patient’s leg if they’re only going to remove it in the ED?” This statement indicates that:",
				"source": "See Effective Team Performance"
			},
			"back": "the EMT’s focus is not on the common goal."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"discuss the problem after the call.",
					"contact the medical director at once.",
					"ignore the problem to avoid conflict.",
					"engage the team member at once."
				],
				"question": "If a problem with a team member is not directly or immediately impacting patient care, the team leader should:",
				"source": "See Troubleshooting Team Conflicts"
			},
			"back": "discuss the problem after the call."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Streamlining",
					"Anchoring",
					"Overconfidence",
					"Bias"
				],
				"question": "Premature diagnosis during a call can be due to what error?",
				"source": "See Critical Thinking and Clinical Decision Making in EMS"
			},
			"back": "Anchoring"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"perform all difficult interventions.",
					"refrain from any direct patient care.",
					"help the team accomplish goals.",
					"command his or her team."
				],
				"question": "An effective team leader should:",
				"source": "See Effective Team Performance"
			},
			"back": "help the team accomplish goals."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"completing the procedure.",
					"solving a clinical problem.",
					"following local protocol.",
					"learning to perform the skill."
				],
				"question": "When the EMT assists a paramedic with an advanced intervention, he or she should recall that the focus of the intervention is on:",
				"source": "See BLS and ALS Providers Working Together"
			},
			"back": "solving a clinical problem."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"common goals.",
					"shared training.",
					"common language.",
					"metric-sized tools."
				],
				"question": "For patient handoff, it is important for EMTs and hospital staff to use:",
				"source": "See Transfer of Patient Care"
			},
			"back": "common language."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"foundational knowledge.",
					"management work.",
					"the chance to replace an EMR.",
					"retraining."
				],
				"question": "To be a great EMT, strive for:",
				"source": "See BLS and ALS Providers Working Together"
			},
			"back": "foundational knowledge."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"discipline.",
					"collaboration.",
					"competition.",
					"rigid protocols."
				],
				"question": "Health care providers who infrequently work together can function effectively as a team if they work in an environment that supports and promotes:",
				"source": "See Types of Teams"
			},
			"back": "collaboration."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"a common set of tasks.",
					"parallel work.",
					"shared transportation.",
					"your own work area."
				],
				"question": "In an independent group, you would have:",
				"source": "See Dependent, Independent, and Interdependent Groups"
			},
			"back": "your own work area."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"the scope of practice.",
					"the standard of care.",
					"patient care advocacy.",
					"the continuum of care."
				],
				"question": "The concept of consistent care across the entire health care team from first patient contact to patient discharge is called:",
				"source": "See An Era of Team Health Care"
			},
			"back": "the continuum of care."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"is not assigned specific roles.",
					"works independently.",
					"does not function under protocols.",
					"works interdependently."
				],
				"question": "In contrast to a health care group, a health care team:",
				"source": "See Groups Versus Teams"
			},
			"back": "works interdependently."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"protocols that allow the EMT to function without medical control.",
					"defining clear roles and responsibilities before the call is received.",
					"rapidly assessing the patient before assigning roles and responsibilities.",
					"a team leader who is capable of performing all of the patient care tasks."
				],
				"question": "The effectiveness of pit crew CPR is dependent on:",
				"source": "See Effective Team Performance"
			},
			"back": "defining clear roles and responsibilities before the call is received."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Data interpretation",
					"Planning",
					"Data gathering",
					"Team communication"
				],
				"question": "Which comes first in EMS decision making?",
				"source": "See Critical Thinking and Clinical Decision Making in EMS"
			},
			"back": "Data gathering"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Suction under direct laryngoscopy",
					"Visualization of the vocal cords",
					"Placement of the endotracheal tube",
					"Preoxygenation with a BVM"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following would the EMT MOST likely be asked to do when assisting a paramedic with endotracheal intubation?",
				"source": "See BLS and ALS Providers Working Together"
			},
			"back": "Preoxygenation with a BVM"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-09-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Clearly identifying your EMS certification level.",
					"Brief pause in care to provide the verbal report.",
					"Providing the handoff report only to a physician.",
					"Use of a mutually agreed-upon handoff format."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following would MOST likely facilitate an accurate and effective verbal handoff report at the hospital?",
				"source": "See Transfer of Patient Care"
			},
			"back": "Use of a mutually agreed-upon handoff format."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-09",
		"label": "Chapter 9"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}